I'm so scared.
Quiet on the set.
Quiet, please.
First positions, please.
Rolling, action.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome back to another edition of Director's Cut.
I am joined here with Bill.
Hello, everybody.
And I'm joined here with Scarlett.
Hi.
And today we're going to talk about, well, it's close to Halloween
and as many of you may or may have not noticed...
Boo.
Yeah, that was scary, Bill.
A lot of TV channels or like a lot of Hollywood scary movies
start coming out and we're going to talk about the top 10
scariest movies of all time.
So not necessarily only horror, but just movies that were
really, really scary.
Is this an official list?
No, it's like kind of my list.
It's your list.
So they might not be very scary at all.
I mean, they were scary for me.
Okay.
All right.
So let's start with number 10.
Is this the least scary?
Yeah, kind of.
Nightmare on Elm Street.
Do you remember that one?
I mean, I haven't seen it, but I know all about it.
Maybe that's...
All right.
That's not what makes it scary, but it's a popular scary movie.
Well, yeah, it's very old.
It's like 1980s.
Even Johnny Depp wasn't the first one, I think.
Really?
I think it was the first or the second one.
The first one, Johnny Depp, wasn't it?
I love Johnny Depp.
And so basically it's about a guy that was killed in a neighborhood
because he was like kidnapping children or something like that.
And so then he kind of comes back as this burnt creature
with like extended knives on his hand.
But the thing is that he would kill you in your dreams.
So you would be afraid of falling asleep
because then that's when he would appear.
And then that's how they confront him too, right?
Right.
You have to confront him in their dreams.
Not in the real world.
Well, so he kills you in his dream.
In your dreams, yeah.
And then you die.
And then you're actually dead.
And you die in real life.
I know this because of The Simpsons, actually,
from the Halloween episode of The Simpsons.
That's probably how I know.
Maybe every single one of these, we'll see.
I don't know the list yet.
But yeah.
Yeah.
Well, it doesn't really make much sense,
like he's killing you in your dreams,
but that's the scary part.
It's just like, how does he do it?
And the thing is that maybe the movie is kind of cheesy.
And I actually saw it again like two weeks ago
or three weeks ago.
And the effects were really cheesy.
But it's actually, if you think about it,
you're like 11 or 12 years old,
and you're afraid of falling asleep because, you know,
you might die.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
All right.
So that's number 10.
Number nine is Poltergeist.
Okay.
You remember Poltergeist?
I haven't seen that.
That's actually probably one of the scariest
movies I ever saw, for the same reason,
because I was only, I think I was only like five,
I was older than five.
Maybe I was like six or seven when I first saw that.
It was the first scary movie I saw,
and it was so damn scary.
It's pretty creepy.
I'm setting it up.
All right.
Poltergeist is, right?
It's like a ghost that you can't really see
and moves things in your house.
Yeah, messes around.
It's like a ghost, yeah.
So basically, that's what the movie's about.
There's this house, I think,
that was like built over these old Indian...
Built over an Indian burial ground.
Yeah.
And so weird things start happening in this house.
But it was like really creepy because, I don't know,
the girl would walk into her living room
or in the kitchen,
and the chairs would be piled up on top of each other
on top of the table.
And like with the little girl on top.
Because they had a little daughter.
Right.
And she was like, yeah,
she was the one that was in most communication
with the Poltergeist.
When I remember,
the children could always communicate with her.
And she went to the other side.
Yeah, and then they had to rescue her.
And they had, yeah.
It was pretty freaky though.
It was pretty scary.
I remember something about they threw up tennis ball
into the other side.
Yeah, to see where they would fall out.
And it was something like...
This is the only time I ever saw it
when I was like six or seven.
So I don't remember a lot of these details,
but the things I do remember are intensely frightening.
Pretty scary, yeah.
How old is the film?
This...
It's also quite old.
Yeah, this film must be like at least 25 years old?
20 years old?
Yeah, yeah.
At least one year old.
A more contemporary one.
Number eight, the film Seven.
You've never seen Seven?
Brad Pitt.
I haven't seen this.
Brad Pitt, Morgan Freeman.
I've already...
I've never seen it.
I've already let our audience know my views on Brad Pitt,
so I'm just going to sit this one out.
Right.
Well, Morgan Freeman's cool though.
I don't have anything against Morgan Freeman.
What if you call the teens Brad Pitt?
I'm not going to go into it.
It's an irrational dislike, okay?
All right, so basically Seven follows this serial killer
who is, at each crime scene,
is sending the message of the seven capital sins.
So like the first one is gluttony and then like lust.
So there's a different message in each murder.
And the movie is kind of twisted the way that he kills people
and what he's doing to them,
but the ending is really unexpected.
It's really, really good.
A twist.
Yeah, because he does the...
In the end, it's the two last capital sins in one.
So it's really, really cool.
You got to see it.
Is that the twist?
Yeah, well...
You just gave it away.
That's part of the twist.
No, no, no.
All right, number seven.
And this is like one of the most famous theme songs.
Psycho.
No.
No?
Norman Bates.
I know that.
Me.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know when he stabs the girl in the shower?
It's a Hitchcock film.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I haven't seen it.
So they're like...
You haven't seen it?
It's the same way as Nightmare on Elm Street.
I feel like I know a lot about it,
but it's like part of the cultural lexicon.
It's like Hitchcock.
This is like...
Yeah, I haven't seen it though, I should see it.
I have seen other Hitchcock, but...
That's...
Yeah, I've seen The Birds and Vertigo.
Vertigo is cool too.
Vertigo is quite good.
Well, Psycho, it's been remade like three or four times, I think.
Right.
But it's really, really good.
Is that the one with China coosinin?
No.
No, that comes later.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay, good.
Well, Psycho is really good.
Number six is the movie The Omen with Damien.
It's the first movie that actually put the Antichrist to the movie screen.
Is this an American film?
That's not the one with the little girl that goes backwards down the stairs.
No, that's The Exorcist.
I haven't seen this either.
All right, The Omen is about the Antichrist coming back, coming to Earth,
and the Antichrist actually comes in the form of a little boy who is put into the household
of this really powerful ambassador, I think it was.
It was the American ambassador in Great Britain or something like that.
But it's really good, and it's really creepy because he's got followers,
and he's got the 666 in his skull, so that's how they find out that it's the Antichrist.
And he's born from a jackal.
Whoa.
I know.
You guys are missing out.
Okay, we'll go see it.
All right, number five, you have to have seen it as well.
Jaws.
Yes, everyone's seen Jaws.
Yeah, I've seen Jaws.
Oh, you haven't seen Jaws?
No, I haven't seen Jaws.
I don't think I've seen all the way through.
It was kind of the Saturday.
But that's not scary.
I'm sorry.
I've seen lots of portions of it on Saturday afternoon.
It's not really scary, the movie, right?
But the next time you go to the beach, you're seriously doubting whether you should get into it.
Like right after you watch the movie.
Yeah.
And then the next time you go to the beach, I hear you.
Yeah, because you're like, where's Jaws?
What's going on?
Jaws is pretty freaky.
Number four is Silence of the Lambs.
Oh, yeah, that's a good one.
All right, so that's more like of a psychological thrill.
Yeah, it's creepy.
It's twisted, right?
Yeah, it's twisted.
Not so much creepy, though.
You don't think it was creepy?
It's creepy, but not scary.
Put the lotion in the basket.
That's from the movie, I'm not just kidding.
Yeah, that was a joke.
It was pretty freaky.
But actually, the crazy thing was that I think it did have certain elements of real mass murders
like Ted Bundy and Jeffrey Dahmer, the famous American psychos.
All right, the next one, number three, is one of the goriest films of all time probably,
The Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
Have you seen that one?
I haven't seen that.
You really picked the wrong people.
I've got the DVD.
I've got the DVD, but I haven't seen it.
Maybe I'll just watch it later.
Well, they did a new version.
Yeah, they remade it.
Yeah, I heard they remade a lot of classic horror movies in the last few years.
Yeah, like Better Special Effects and everything.
It's creepy, it's scary, but there's a lot of blood and gore in this movie.
It's more gruesome.
It's very, very gruesome.
All right, number two.
I don't get the appeal of those films, like Saw.
It's awful.
Well, what about Saw?
Saw is like...
Hostel and stuff like that.
It's just...
Well, Saw and Hostel, they're very gory, but...
That's it.
It's just a gimmick.
I hate that stuff.
I watched Saw, and it was literally the most boring movie ever saw in my entire life.
We looked sad.
Oh, I was scared.
That was the first one, and they've already made another six of them with the same exact
plot, the same exact...
So five, so what was it?
I think the thing about Saw, what I liked about it is, how does this guy come up with
these things?
Yeah, he's imaginative.
The person that's writing these things up is really creative and kind of twisted.
Or a bit sick.
Can you imagine living with this guy or like being married to him?
He's probably like the nicest guy in the world.
Yeah, really?
He's a bit dark.
He's got like two golden retrievers.
I'm sure.
He's got to be like the sunniest, happiest dude.
The children and everything.
All right, so number two is the one that you were talking about, The Exorcist.
Hey, I know that.
Yeah, I would put that, yeah, I'd say that.
That is not too scary.
All right, so that was 1980s as well.
The music was creepy.
Seven days, I believe.
It's maybe late 70s.
The music was really creepy.
Oh, very creepy.
Everything is really scary about that movie.
Especially that scene where he comes down the stairs, walking backwards.
I think that's a recent edition.
That wasn't in the original edition.
Oh, really?
Yeah, they just cut it out of the original edition, I think.
Well, there was a lot of controversy around this film, right?
Because, for example, I think there were some elements that the church really opposed.
Well, because they say the church doesn't do exorcisms anymore.
I'm not Catholic.
And then there's this whole thing about how during filming of The Exorcist,
two or three people of the cast died.
Really?
Yeah, like a cameraman and then some other person, they died.
So then people were just like, this is like messing with the unknown.
It's really creepy.
It's like messing with King Tut's tomb.
Yeah, it's not like that.
It's a curse.
It is terribly scary, though.
The part when she throws up was pretty gruesome.
Oh, yeah.
That part is kind of funny.
Well, it's funny because now you see it in that other movie.
What was that scary movie?
They make fun of it.
Well, yeah, it's the same thing.
It's such a popular and so ingrained in our popular culture.
The star was mine.
That's also from the movie.
That's what she says.
Thanks.
Number one, Jack Nicholson in The Shining.
I'm glad that's your number one.
That's a good number one.
Yeah, I agree with that.
That's a really complete kind of scary movie, I think.
Because it's creepy, has like an open ending open to interpretation.
It's a Stanley Kubrick film, too, so it's shot really beautifully.
And Jack Nicholson is really good in it.
Jack Nicholson is great.
Yeah, he was really good in there.
Olive Oil's in it.
I don't know.
She played Olive Oil, but she was a dandy's mother.
I don't remember.
But, yeah, I think the freakiest thing about the movie is the scene that's the most popular now
is when the kid is on the big wheel on the little tricycle,
and he's riding around, and then he turns on the hallway, and he's got two twins.
And he's like, come with us.
Come play with us.
The British twins.
And you're like, what?
It's really creepy.
That is really creepy.
Scary British twins.
If they were American, it wouldn't be nearly.
Yeah, that's why they were British, because that makes it easy.
I thought, I mean, it's not really scary, but the end, the very, very end, where,
well, I don't want to give it away.
I don't want to give it away.
But you guys know what I'm talking about, and that's creepy.
Yeah, it is.
The photographic photograph at the very end.
Yeah.
It's such an open-ended thing.
I think that's Kubrick.
That's Kubrick's doing more than Stephen King.
Stephen King wrote the original book.
I feel like that kind of weird open-ended.
I'm actually surprised I didn't put any Stephen King in here.
Well, he did, at number one.
Well, yeah, but apart from this, he's made some really good ones.
Like, for example, we were talking about It the other day.
That was like a three-hour long film, which was like, it wasn't really made for the cinema.
It was like for TV.
It was really scary, though.
It's about a clown, and that's why I'm like one of the reasons why I'm really, really afraid of clowns.
Can we do an honorable mention for, I guess, just anything that David Lynch does?
Do you guys like David Lynch?
Like what?
Mulholland Drive is probably the creepiest David Lynch movie ever.
Have you seen it?
No.
Have you seen any David Lynch movies?
Well, it's creepy.
Any more examples?
I mean, he did Twin Peaks, the whole series.
That's not really a scary anything.
I did put, as an honorable mention, I did put Carrie.
That was pretty scary.
Have you seen Carrie?
That's Stephen King as well.
That is Stephen King, I think.
She pours the blood all over the table.
Yeah, Carrie is like this.
It's really creepy because it's about kind of like teenage angst.
But like she has this fanatic mother who's like really, really Catholic.
So there are all these like Catholic elements in there that in the movie, they're made really,
really creepy.
And then like everyone teases her and like she's like an outcast in high school and
she's like really, really weird.
And then they're like in their prom and as a prank, they choose her to be like the prom
queen.
And then when she comes up on stage, they like pour pig's blood all over her.
Nice.
And that's like the last straw.
And apparently she just gets like these weird mental powers and it just like starts creating havoc
on the entire party and like people start dying.
It's really cool.
That sounds awesome.
It is awesome.
It's scary.
That's like we're liberating it.
It is.
I always wished I could do that in high school.
Throughout the movie, you're just like feeling sorry for this girl and you're like,
oh God, why are they being so meaner?
And then when she like gets these powers and starts like kicking the crap out of everyone,
you're like, yes, revenge.
Really?
That's like what people want to see, I think.
Totally.
All right.
And probably the worst movie of all time, which is like scary movie, is probably a Friday
the 13th.
Yeah.
Oh, that just annoys me with them.
Jason?
Jason.
Oh, okay.
Is that with Jamie Lee Curtis?
No, that was Halloween.
That annoys me, that film.
And that was also bad.
I'm not a big Jamie Lee Curtis fan.
All right.
There are about 10 choices or a couple of honorable mentions there.
So if you haven't seen them, take advantage of the fact that it's Halloween.
Boo.
Go and watch a movie, a scary movie, and yeah, get scared.
I don't know why people don't like to get scared.
They do.
That's why we have things like scary movies.
No, but like for example, I couldn't do this show with Liliana because she's completely
afraid of scary movies.
Oh, it's because she hasn't seen any of them.
No, no.
She can't even talk about them.
She can't talk about them.
She can't watch a scary movie.
And then she would have nightmares and she can't sleep for a week.
Yeah.
I've known people with similar afflictions.
Really?
Yeah.
I think it's like their memories are just too vivid.
Too vivid.
Yeah.
Like you can just always recall those weird things, those bad, bad images.
Sorry, images.
I just can't let it go.
All right, guys.
That's all for today.
We'll see you guys next time and be sure to watch some of these scary flicks.
Until next time.
Bye.